Ceremonies and Events Office fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
Ceremonies and Events Office fonds
1963-2023, predominant 1963-1995
F-91
3.41 m of textual records
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department Maggie Benston Student Services Building, Rm. 0400 8888 University Dr. Burnaby British Columbia Canada V5A 1S6 Telephone: 778.782.3805 Email: archives@sfu.ca http://www.sfu.ca/archives
DATES OF CREATION The predominant dates are 1963-1995. The only records that post-date 1995 are the Convocation booklets that are received twice yearly by the Archives and added to the fonds.
Ceremonies and Events Office
The Ceremonies and Events Office manages and produces Simon Fraser University's ceremonial, social, fundraising and special events and maintains SFU's traditions and protocol. It is the main office (along with the Registrar's Office) responsible for Spring and Fall Convocation ceremonies.
The Office coordinates many other events throughout the year, primarily for the President's Office, University Advancement and Alumni Relations. The office responsibilities include formal university events such as building openings; ceremonies such as SFU Remembers; donor recognition events; staff/employee recognition and awards events.
Prior to 1982, the Registrar's Office was responsible for convocation ceremonies, while the President's Office organized other ceremonial functions. Over the years, the title "Ceremonies Officer" was used by various university staff in the Registrar's Office.
In February 1982 the position of Director of Ceremonies was formally created when Donna Laws, assumed this position in addition to her role as Secretary to the Board of Governors. She held both positions until her retirement in 1993, when she was succeeded as Director of Ceremonies by her long-time associate, Marilyn Pankratz. The position of Secretary to the Board of Governors was taken over by another university staff member.
The Director of Ceremonies reported to the Vice-President, University Development until 1987, when the reporting relationship changed to the Vice-President for SFU at Harbour Centre (1987-1992), Vice-President Harbour Centre and External Relations (1992-1994), Office of the President (1994-2002), and the Vice-President, University Advancement (2002-).
Chief officers:
* Donna Laws, Director, 1982 - 1993
* Marilyn Pankratz, Director, 1993 - 2004
* Holli Edgelow, Director, 2004 -
published
Full
Revised
Title of the fonds is based on the name of its creator.
Fonds consists of records relating to University ceremonies created by the Office of Ceremonies since 1982, and before that time, by the Registrar's Office and the President's Office. Activities and topics documented include the opening ceremonies for SFU in 1965, convocations, awards ceremonies, building and room openings and dedications, donor recognition events, staff recognition events, installations of presidents and chancellors, university anniversaries, and other special ceremonies.
Records include programs, books of words (order of proceedings), invitations, guest lists, correspondence, notes, press clippings, news releases, publications, photographic material, and other documents.
The records were arranged by the archivist.
Pankratz, Marilyn; Laws, Donna; Edgelow, Holli; Events and celebrations
The records were acquired from the Ceremonies and Events Office in a number of accessions.
Further accruals are expected.
Access to some files within this fonds is restricted in accordance with Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy legislation. Please consult the series descriptions, the unit lists, and the archivist for further details.
- SFU Opening ceremonies files, 1963 - 1965; F-91-1; 9 cm of textual records
  published
  Series consists of records relating to the opening ceremonies of Simon Fraser University on September 9, 1965. Activities documented include the planning of the ceremonies. Records include programs, correspondence, notes, news clippings, publications, sheet music, charter student certificate, and other documents.
  Some of the files in this series were originally in the fonds of the Office of the President and were placed in the Ceremonies Fonds by previous archives staff.
  Files were arranged by the archivist.
  No further accruals are expected.
  Access to files containing third-party personal information may be restricted. Please see the file list and consult with the archivist for more details.
  A file list is available.
  - Opening of SFU - newsclippings, vol. 1, 1963 - 1965; F-91-1-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 91-1)
    Textual records
    Open
  - Opening of SFU - newsclippings, vol. 2, 1963 - 1965; F-91-1-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 91-1)
  - Opening ceremonies - program, 1965; F-91-1-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 91-1)
    - SFU opening ceremonies program book, 1965; F-91-1-0-0-3-1; Ceremonies and Events Office
      The Ceremonies and Events Office manages and produces Simon Fraser University's ceremonial, social, fundraising and special events and maintains SFU's traditions and protocol. It is the main office (along with the Registrar's Office) responsible for Spring and Fall Convocation ceremonies.
      The Office coordinates many other events throughout the year, primarily for the President's Office, University Advancement and Alumni Relations. The office responsibilities include formal university events such as building openings; ceremonies such as SFU Remembers; donor recognition events; staff/employee recognition and awards events.
      Prior to 1982, the Registrar's Office was responsible for convocation ceremonies, while the President's Office organized other ceremonial functions. Over the years, the title "Ceremonies Officer" was used by various university staff in the Registrar's Office.
      In February 1982 the position of Director of Ceremonies was formally created when Donna Laws, assumed this position in addition to her role as Secretary to the Board of Governors. She held both positions until her retirement in 1993, when she was succeeded as Director of Ceremonies by her long-time associate, Marilyn Pankratz. The position of Secretary to the Board of Governors was taken over by another university staff member.
      The Director of Ceremonies reported to the Vice-President, University Development until 1987, when the reporting relationship changed to the Vice-President for SFU at Harbour Centre (1987-1992), Vice-President Harbour Centre and External Relations (1992-1994), Office of the President (1994-2002), and the Vice-President, University Advancement (2002-).
      Chief officers:
      * Donna Laws, Director, 1982 - 1993
      * Marilyn Pankratz, Director, 1993 - 2004
      * Holli Edgelow, Director, 2004 -
  - Opening ceremonies - correspondence, vol. 1, 1964 - 1965; F-91-1-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 91-1)
    Pending review
  - Opening ceremonies - correspondence, vol. 2, 1964 - 1965; F-91-1-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 91-1)
  - Opening ceremonies - music (Paul Reif), 1965; F-91-1-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 91-1)
  - Opening ceremonies - Charter Student certificates, 1965; F-91-1-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 91-1)
  - Opening ceremonies - Lord Lovat, 1965; F-91-1-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 91-1)
- Installation ceremonies files, 1965 - 1983; F-91-2; 12 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to the installation of the Presidents and Chancellors of SFU including Patrick Mc-Taggart Cowan as President and Gordon Shrum as Chancellor (1965); Pauline Jewett as President (1974) and William Saywell as President (1983). Records include programs, invitations, guest lists, books of words (order of proceedings), timetables, correspondence, notes, publications, press releases, news clippings, speeches, minutes, photographs, and other documents.
  Further accruals are expected.
  For information on the installations of John Stubbs as President and Joseph Segal as Chancellor in 1993, see the October 1993 Fall Convocation file. For information on the installation of Milton Wong as Chancellor in 1999 see the October 1999 Fall Convocation File.
  - Installation ceremonies - McTaggart-Cowan, Shrum; program, 1965; F-91-2-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 91-1)
    - SFU installation ceremonies program book, 1965; F-91-2-0-0-1-1; Ceremonies and Events Office
  - Installation ceremonies - McTaggart-Cowan, Shrum; correspondence, 1965; F-91-2-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 91-1)
  - Installation ceremony - Jewett, vol. 1, 1974; F-91-2-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 91-1)
  - Installation ceremony - Jewett, vol. 2, 1974; F-91-2-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 91-2)
  - Installation ceremony - Saywell, vol. 1, 1983; F-91-2-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 91-2)
  - Installation ceremony - Saywell, vol. 2, 1983; F-91-2-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 91-2)
  - Installation ceremony - Saywell, vol. 3, 1983; F-91-2-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 91-2)
- Convocation files, 2015; 1967-2023; F-91-3; 1.69 m of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to the convocation ceremonies held at SFU to award undergraduate, graduate, and honorary degrees. Records include Convocation booklet, programs, invitations, guest lists, books of words (order of proceedings), timetables, correspondence, notes, publications, press releases, news clippings, speeches, and other documents.
  Note that files from 1990s onwards contain fewer document types, often only the Convocation booklet and book of words; and from 2006 only the Convocation booklet. The format of the booklet changed little from 1967 to 2005. Since ca. 2006, the booklet has been produced by Communication Services, a unit of Student Services (the Spring 2006 booklet is the first to credit Student Services).
  Archives and Records Management Department; Textual records; Records in electronic form (digitized)
  Convocation booklets are available in both hardcopy and PDF. The Archives digitized the run of hardcopies from 1967 to 2014; these are directly available in SFU AtoM. From 2015 onwards, the Archives receives both the hardcopy and a PDF directly from Student Services.
  - Convocation May 1967, F-91-3-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 91-2)
    Textual records; Records in electronic form (digitized)
    - 1967 May 20 convocation program, F-91-3-0-0-1-1
      Pages 2, 10, 11 and 12 intentionally left blank.
  - Convocation May 1968, F-91-3-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 91-2)
    - 1968 May 11 convocation program, F-91-3-0-0-2-1
  - Convocation May 1969, F-91-3-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 91-3)
    - 1969 May 24 convocation program, F-91-3-0-0-3-1
  - Convocation May 1970, F-91-3-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 91-3)
    - 1970 May 23 convocation program, F-91-3-0-0-4-1
  - Convocation May 1971, F-91-3-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 91-3)
    - 1971 May 29 convocation program, F-91-3-0-0-5-1; Ceremonies and Events Office
  - Convocation May 1972, F-91-3-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 91-3)
    - 1972 May 27 convocation program, F-91-3-0-0-6-1
  - Convocation May 1973, F-91-3-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 91-3)
    - 1973 May 26 convocation program, F-91-3-0-0-7-1
  - Convocation May 1974, F-91-3-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 91-3)
    - 1974 May 25 convocation program, F-91-3-0-0-8-1
  - Convocation May 1975, F-91-3-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 91-3)
    - 1975 May 24 convocation program, F-91-3-0-0-9-1
  - Convocation May 1976, F-91-3-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 91-4)
    - Convocation, Saturday May 29, 1976, F-91-3-0-0-10-1
  - Convocation May 1977, F-91-3-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 91-4)
    - Convocation, Saturday May 28, 1977, F-91-3-0-0-11-1
  - Convocation May 1978, F-91-3-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 91-4)
    - Convocation, Saturday May 27, 1978, F-91-3-0-0-12-1
  - Convocation June 1979, F-91-3-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 91-4)
    - 1979 June 2 convocation program, F-91-3-0-0-13-1; Ceremonies and Events Office
  - Convocation June 1980, F-91-3-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 91-4)
    - 1980 June 7 convocation program, F-91-3-0-0-14-1; Ceremonies and Events Office
  - Convocation June 1981, F-91-3-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 91-5)
    - 1981 June 6 convocation program, F-91-3-0-0-15-1; Ceremonies and Events Office
  - Convocation June 1982, F-91-3-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 91-5)
    - 1982 June 5 convocation program, F-91-3-0-0-16-1; Ceremonies and Events Office
  - Convocation June 1983, F-91-3-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 91-5)
    - 1983 June 4 convocation program, F-91-3-0-0-17-1; Ceremonies and Events Office
  - Convocation June 1984, F-91-3-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 91-5)
    - 1984 June 9 convocation program, F-91-3-0-0-18-1; Ceremonies and Events Office
  - Convocation June 1985, vol. 1, F-91-3-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 91-5)
    - 1985 June 7-8 convocation program, F-91-3-0-0-19-1; Ceremonies and Events Office
  - Convocation June 1985, vol. 2, F-91-3-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 91-5)
  - Convocation June 1986, F-91-3-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 91-6)
    - 1986 June 6-7 convocation program, F-91-3-0-0-21-1; Ceremonies and Events Office
  - Convocation June 1987, F-91-3-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 91-6)
    - 1987 June 4-5 convocation program, F-91-3-0-0-22-1; Ceremonies and Events Office
  - Convocation June 1988, vol. 1, F-91-3-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 91-6)
    - 1988 June 2-3 convocation program, F-91-3-0-0-23-1; Ceremonies and Events Office
  - Convocation June 1988, vol. 2, F-91-3-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 91-6)
  - Convocation June 1989, F-91-3-0-0-25 (Archival box - standard 91-7)
    - 1989 June 8-9 convocation program, F-91-3-0-0-25-1; Ceremonies and Events Office
  - Convocation June 1990, F-91-3-0-0-26 (Archival box - standard 91-7)
    - 1990 June 7-8 convocation program, F-91-3-0-0-26-1; Ceremonies and Events Office
  - Convocation October 1990, F-91-3-0-0-27 (Archival box - standard 91-7)
    - 1990 Oct 12 convocation program, F-91-3-0-0-27-1; Ceremonies and Events Office
  - Convocation June 1991, F-91-3-0-0-28 (Archival box - standard 91-7)
    - 1991 June convocation program, F-91-3-0-0-28-1; Ceremonies and Events Office
  - Convocation October 1991, F-91-3-0-0-29 (Archival box - standard 91-7)
    - 1991 Oct convocation program, F-91-3-0-0-29-1; Ceremonies and Events Office
  - Convocation June 1992, F-91-3-0-0-30 (Archival box - standard 91-8)
    - 1992 June convocation program, F-91-3-0-0-30-1; Ceremonies and Events Office
  - Convocation October 1992, F-91-3-0-0-31 (Archival box - standard 91-8)
    - 1992 Oct convocation program, F-91-3-0-0-31-1; Ceremonies and Events Office
      Architectural drawings
  - Convocation June 1993, vol. 1, F-91-3-0-0-32 (Archival box - standard 91-8)
    - 1993 June convocation program, F-91-3-0-0-32-1; Ceremonies and Events Office
  - Convocation June 1993, vol. 2, F-91-3-0-0-33 (Archival box - standard 91-8)
  - Convocation October 1993, vol. 1, F-91-3-0-0-34 (Archival box - standard 91-8)
    - 1993 October convocation program, F-91-3-0-0-34-1
  - Convocation October 1993, vol. 2, F-91-3-0-0-35 (Archival box - standard 91-8)
  - Convocation June 1994, vol. 1, F-91-3-0-0-36 (Archival box - standard 91-9)
    - 1994 June convocation program, F-91-3-0-0-38-1; Ceremonies and Events Office
  - Convocation June 1994, vol. 2, F-91-3-0-0-37 (Archival box - standard 91-9)
  - Convocation October 1994, F-91-3-0-0-38 (Archival box - standard 91-9)
    - 1994 Oct convocation program, F-91-3-0-0-38-2; Ceremonies and Events Office
  - Convocation June 1995, F-91-3-0-0-39 (Archival box - standard 91-9)
    - 1995 June convocation program, F-91-3-0-0-39-1; Ceremonies and Events Office
  - Convocation October 1995, F-91-3-0-0-40 (Archival box - standard 91-9)
    - 1995 Oct convocation program, F-91-3-0-0-40-1; Ceremonies and Events Office
  - Convocation June 1996, F-91-3-0-0-41 (Archival box - standard 91-10)
    - 1996 June convocation program, F-91-3-0-0-41-1; Ceremonies and Events Office
  - Convocation October 1996, F-91-3-0-0-42 (Archival box - standard 91-10)
    - 1996 Oct convocation program, F-91-3-0-0-42-1; Ceremonies and Events Office
  - Convocation June 1997, F-91-3-0-0-43 (Archival box - standard 91-10)
    - 1997 June convocation program, F-91-3-0-0-43-1; Ceremonies and Events Office
  - Convocation October 1997, F-91-3-0-0-44 (Archival box - standard 91-10)
    - 1997 Oct convocation program, F-91-3-0-0-44-1; Ceremonies and Events Office
  - Convocation June 1998, F-91-3-0-0-45 (Archival box - standard 91-10)
    - 1998 June convocation program, F-91-3-0-0-45-1; Ceremonies and Events Office
  - Convocation October 1998, F-91-3-0-0-46 (Archival box - standard 91-11)
    - 1998 Oct convocation program, F-91-3-0-0-46-1; Ceremonies and Events Office
  - Convocation June 1999, F-91-3-0-0-47 (Archival box - standard 91-11)
    - 1999 June convocation program, F-91-3-0-0-47-1; Ceremonies and Events Office
  - Convocation October 1999, F-91-3-0-0-48 (Archival box - standard 91-11)
    - 1999 Oct convocation program, F-91-3-0-0-48-1; Ceremonies and Events Office
  - Convocation June 2000, F-91-3-0-0-49 (Archival box - standard 91-11)
    - 2000 June convocation program, F-91-3-0-0-49-1; Ceremonies and Events Office
  - Convocation October 2000, F-91-3-0-0-50 (Archival box - standard 91-12)
    - 2000 Oct convocation program, F-91-3-0-0-50-1; Ceremonies and Events Office
  - Convocation June 2001, F-91-3-0-0-51 (Archival box - standard 91-12)
    - 2001 June convocation program, F-91-3-0-0-51-1; Ceremonies and Events Office
  - Convocation October 2001, F-91-3-0-0-52 (Archival box - standard 91-12)
    - 2001 Oct convocaton program, F-91-3-0-0-52-1; Ceremonies and Events Office
  - Convocation June 2002, F-91-3-0-0-53 (Archival box - standard 91-12)
    - 2002 June convocation program, F-91-3-0-0-53-1; Ceremonies and Events Office
  - Convocation October 2002, F-91-3-0-0-54 (Archival box - standard 91-12)
    - 2002 Oct convocation program, F-91-3-0-0-54-1; Ceremonies and Events Office
  - Convocation, June 2003, vol. 1, F-91-3-0-0-55 (Archival box - standard 91-24)
    - 2003 June convocation program, F-91-3-0-0-55-1; Ceremonies and Events Office
  - Convocation, June 2003, vol. 2, F-91-3-0-0-56 (Archival box - standard 91-24)
  - Convocation, October 2003, vol. 1, F-91-3-0-0-57 (Archival box - standard 91-24)
    - 2003 Oct convocation program, F-91-3-0-0-57-1; Ceremonies and Events Office
  - Convocation, October 2003, vol. 2, F-91-3-0-0-58 (Archival box - standard 91-24)
  - Convocation, June 2004, vol. 1, F-91-3-0-0-59 (Archival box - standard 91-24)
    - 2004 June convocation program, F-91-3-0-0-59-1; Ceremonies and Events Office
  - Convocation, June 2004, vol. 2, F-91-3-0-0-60 (Archival box - standard 91-24)
  - Convocation, October 2004, vol. 1, F-91-3-0-0-61 (Archival box - standard 91-25)
    - 2004 Oct convocation program, F-91-3-0-0-61-1; Ceremonies and Events Office
  - Convocation, October 2004, vol. 2, F-91-3-0-0-62 (Archival box - standard 91-25)
  - Convocation, June 2005, vol. 1, F-91-3-0-0-63 (Archival box - standard 91-25)
    - 2005 June convocation program, F-91-3-0-0-63-1; Ceremonies and Events Office
  - Convocation, June 2005, vol. 2, F-91-3-0-0-64 (Archival box - standard 91-25)
  - Convocation, October 2005, vol. 1, F-91-3-0-0-65 (Archival box - standard 91-25)
    - 2005 Oct convocation program, F-91-3-0-0-65-1; Ceremonies and Events Office
  - Convocation, October 2005, vol. 2, F-91-3-0-0-66 (Archival box - standard 91-25)
  - Convocation, June 2006, F-91-3-0-0-67 (Archival box - standard 91-25)
    - 2006 June convocation program, F-91-3-0-0-67-1; Ceremonies and Events Office
  - Convocation, October 2006, F-91-3-0-0-68 (Archival box - standard 91-25)
    - 2006 Oct convocation program, F-91-3-0-0-68-1; Ceremonies and Events Office
  - Convocation, June 2007, F-91-3-0-0-69 (Archival box - small 91-28)
    - 2007 June convocation program, F-91-3-0-0-69-1; Ceremonies and Events Office
  - Convocation, October 2007, F-91-3-0-0-70 (Archival box - small 91-28)
    - 2007 Oct convocation program, F-91-3-0-0-70-1; Ceremonies and Events Office
  - Convocation, June 2008, F-91-3-0-0-71 (Archival box - small 91-28)
    - 2008 June convocation program, F-91-3-0-0-71-1
  - Convocation, October 2008, F-91-3-0-0-72 (Archival box - small 91-28)
    - 2008 Oct convocation program, F-91-3-0-0-72-1; Ceremonies and Events Office
  - Convocation, June 2009, F-91-3-0-0-73 (Archival box - small 91-28)
    - 2009 June convocation program, F-91-3-0-0-73-1; Ceremonies and Events Office
  - Convocation, October 2009, F-91-3-0-0-74 (Archival box - small 91-28)
    - 2009 Oct convocation program, F-91-3-0-0-74-1; Ceremonies and Events Office
  - Convocation, June 2010, F-91-3-0-0-75 (Archival box - standard 91-29)
    - 2010 June convocation program, F-91-3-0-0-75-1; Ceremonies and Events Office
  - Convocation, October 2010, F-91-3-0-0-76 (Archival box - standard 91-29)
    - 2010 Oct convocation program, F-91-3-0-0-76-1; Ceremonies and Events Office
  - Convocation, June 2011, F-91-3-0-0-77 (Archival box - standard 91-29)
    - 2011 June convocation program, F-91-3-0-0-77-1; Ceremonies and Events Office
  - Convocation, October 2011, F-91-3-0-0-78 (Archival box - standard 91-29)
    - 2011 Oct convocation program, F-91-3-0-0-78-1; Ceremonies and Events Office
  - Convocation, June 2012, F-91-3-0-0-79 (Archival box - standard 91-29)
    - 2012 June convocation program, F-91-3-0-0-79-1; Ceremonies and Events Office
  - Convocation, October 2012, F-91-3-0-0-80 (Archival box - standard 91-29)
    - 2012 Oct convocation program, F-91-3-0-0-80-1; Ceremonies and Events Office
  - Convocation, June 2013, F-91-3-0-0-81 (Archival box - standard 91-29)
    - 2013 June Convocation book, F-91-3-0-0-81-1
      Textual records; Records in electronic form (born-digital)
  - Convocation, October 2013, F-91-3-0-0-82 (Archival box - standard 91-29)
    - 2013 Oct convocation program, F-91-3-0-0-82-1; Ceremonies and Events Office
  - Convocation, June 2014, F-91-3-0-0-83 (Archival box - standard 91-29)
    - 2014 spring convocation program, F-91-3-0-0-83-1; Ceremonies and Events Office
  - Convocation, October 2014, F-91-3-0-0-84 (Archival box - standard 91-29)
    - Fall Convocation 2014, F-91-3-0-0-84-1; Ceremonies and Events Office
  - Convocation, June 2015, F-91-3-0-0-85 (Newspaper box 91-30)
    - Spring Convocation 2015, F-91-3-0-0-85-1
  - Convocation, October 2015, F-91-3-0-0-86 (Newspaper box 91-30)
    - Fall Convocation 2015, F-91-3-0-0-86-1
  - Convocation, June 2016, F-91-3-0-0-87 (Newspaper box 91-30)
    - Spring Convocation 2016, F-91-3-0-0-87-1
  - Convocation, October 2016, F-91-3-0-0-88 (Newspaper box 91-30)
    - Fall Convocation 2016, F-91-3-0-0-88-1
  - Convocation, June 2017, F-91-3-0-0-89 (Newspaper box 91-30)
    - Simon Fraser University Convocation Spring 2017, F-91-3-0-0-89-1
  - Convocation, October 2017, F-91-3-0-0-90 (Newspaper box 91-30)
    - Simon Fraser University Convocation Fall 2017, F-91-3-0-0-90-1
  - Convocation, June 2018, F-91-3-0-0-91 (Newspaper box 91-30)
    - Simon Fraser University Convocation June 2018, f-91-3-0-0-91-1
  - Convocation, Fall 2018, F-91-3-0-0-92 (Archival box - standard 91-31)
    - Simon Fraser University Convocation Fall 2018, F-91-3-0-0-92-1
  - Convocation, Spring 2019, F-91-3-0-0-93
    Hardcopy and pdf (born-digital) available.
    - SFU Spring 2019 Convocation, F-91-3-0-0-93-1
  - Convocation Fall 2019, F-91-3-0-0-94 (Archival box - standard 91-31)
    - SFU Fall 2019 Convocation, F-91-3-0-0-94-1
  - Convocation Spring 2020, F-91-3-0-0-95
    Due to COVID-19, SFU did not hold an in-person Convocation ceremony for Spring 2020.
    - Convocation Spring 2020
  - Convocation Fall 2020 (3 volumes), F-91-3-0-0-96